<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Benson Masons on John J Mercer | A.F. &amp; A.M.</title>
    <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Benson Masons on John J Mercer | A.F. &amp; A.M.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://dev.bensonmasons.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2024 Dues</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/dues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/dues/</guid>
      <description>Dues season is here and online payment is available!&#xA;OR You can pay through the Grand View Member Portal&#xA;Dues for 2024 are $95.50 and are explained below:&#xA;Description Amount Grand Lodge Per Capita Tax (Breakout Below) $37.00 - Grand Lodge of NE General Fund $31.00 - Nebraska Masonic Home $2.50 - Masonic-Eastern Star Home for Children $1.50 - George Washington Masonic Memorial $1.50 - Masonic Education Newsletter $0.50 Grand Lodge Assessments (Breakout Below) $3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 Officers</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/officers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/officers/</guid>
      <description>2024 Elected and Appointed Lodge Officers From left to right: Bro. Ethan White (Senior Deacon) / WB John Dimon (Treasurer) / Bro. Celio Santos (Senior Warden) / WB Michael Barnes (Worshipful Master) / Bro. Mark Beneda (Junior Warden) / WB Brent Marriott (Secretary) / Bro. Julius Boatwright (Junior Deacon) / WB Eric BenSalah* (Chaplain)&#xA;* = Pictured in Grand Lodge attire as the Grand Marshal due to being Installing Master for the 2024 Installation of Officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/about/</guid>
      <description>As Freemasons The Brethren of John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 believe that while there are many different paths a Freemason may follow: educational, ritual, community, philanthropy, &amp;hellip;, etc. We believe that the best way to observe the Craft is through a Brotherhood focused on learning and understanding our ritual and then applying its teachings to ourselves and to the communities in which we live.&#xA;To that end, Mercer places a strong emphasis on tangible Masonic education and are purposeful in the selection of candidates to join us in this great and good work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calendar</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/calendar/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Whether you have questions about building rentals, becoming a Mason, or just want to know more about who we are and how we can help the community, send us a message and we’d be happy to get back to you!&#xA;General Inquiries: info@bensonmasons.com&#xA;Hall Rental Inquiries: rentals@bensonmasons.com or (402) 553-0679&#xA;5903 Maple St. Omaha, NE 68104&#xA;NOTE: If you plan to visit the Lodge in person, please make sure to schedule an appointment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hall Rental</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/hall-rental/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/hall-rental/</guid>
      <description>The Benson Masonic Temple’s dining hall is available for rent for your event. The hall is open for rent on Fridays, Saturdays and Sundays unless an event is already scheduled.&#xA;Some facts, photos and further information about the hall are outlined below.&#xA;Please read the Hall Information &amp; Cost Requirements below before submitting a request. If, after reading the information below, you have additional questions, please email us at rentals@bensonmasons.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notables</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/more/notables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/more/notables/</guid>
      <description>2023 Rock Maul Award (Large Lodge) John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 At the 2023 Annual Communication of the Grand Lodge of Nebraska, John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 repeated as winners of the Rock Maul Award (Large Lodge). The Rock Maul Award is bestowed by the Grand Master, upon the recommendation of the Grand Lodge Awards Committee, to a large lodge and a small lodge whose works represent the best well-rounded large and small lodges in Nebraska.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Patron Saints and the Point Within A Circle</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/more/the-patron-saints-and-the-point-within-a-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/more/the-patron-saints-and-the-point-within-a-circle/</guid>
      <description>John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 is selling prints of the painting “The Patron Saints and the Point within A Circle” commissioned by the Lodge in 2014.&#xA;For more information on this inspirational work of Masonic art, please have a look at the Interview with WB. David Long&#xA;Patron Saints and the Point Within the Circle Shipping Information All prints are shipped in 24″ x 4″ mailing tubes using ground shipping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Events</title>
      <link>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/more/upcoming-public-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dev.bensonmasons.com/more/upcoming-public-events/</guid>
      <description>The Brethren of John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 often engage with their local community, whether through events open to the public or attending public events. Check out our upcoming public engagement events below – we hope to see you there! Note: ALL events listed below are OPEN to the PUBLIC.&#xA;All events are at the Benson Masonic Temple (5903 Maple St) unless otherwise noted.&#xA;2024&#xA;January 6, 2024&#xA;Annual Officer Installation</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
