<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates on John J Mercer | A.F. &amp; A.M.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Updates on John J Mercer | A.F. &amp; A.M.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notables</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/updates/notables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/updates/notables/</guid>
      <description>2023 Rock Maul Award (Large Lodge) John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 At the 2023 Annual Communication of the Grand Lodge of Nebraska, John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 repeated as winners of the Rock Maul Award (Large Lodge). The Rock Maul Award is bestowed by the Grand Master, upon the recommendation of the Grand Lodge Awards Committee, to a large lodge and a small lodge whose works represent the best well-rounded large and small lodges in Nebraska.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Patron Saints and the Point Within A Circle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/updates/the-patron-saints-and-the-point-within-a-circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/updates/the-patron-saints-and-the-point-within-a-circle/</guid>
      <description>John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 is selling prints of the painting, &amp;ldquo;The Patron Saints and the Point within A Circle&amp;rdquo; commissioned by the Lodge in 2014.&#xA;For more information on this inspirational work of Masonic art, please have a look at the Interview with WB. David Long&#xA;Patron Saints and the Point Within the Circle Shipping Information All prints are shipped in 24&amp;quot; x 4&amp;quot; mailing tubes using ground shipping.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Events</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/updates/upcoming-public-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/updates/upcoming-public-events/</guid>
      <description>The Brethren of John J. Mercer Lodge No. 290 often engage with their local community, whether through events open to the public or attending public events. Check out our upcoming public engagement events below – we hope to see you there! Note: ALL events listed below are OPEN to the PUBLIC.&#xA;All events are at the Benson Masonic Temple (5903 Maple St) unless otherwise noted.&#xA;2024&#xA;January 6, 2024&#xA;Annual Officer Installation</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
